<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Forecasting for Social Good</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Forecasting for Social Good</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:15:26 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>F4SG annual workshop</title>
      <link>/services/f4sg-workshoop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/f4sg-workshoop/</guid>
      <description>This is an annual workshop sponsored by the International Institute of Forecasters
Forecasting for Social Good Workshop While there is a growing recognition by agencies, organizations, and governments that data-driven decision making tools, like forecasting models, can offer significant improvements to the societies they are working to improve, there is not a cohesive body of research that offers guidance on how to best implement, understand, use, and evaluate forecasting methods for societal impact in practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bahman Rostami-Tabar</title>
      <link>/team/bahman-rostami/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/bahman-rostami/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F4SG Research Network</title>
      <link>/services/network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/network/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael D. Porter</title>
      <link>/team/mike-porter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/mike-porter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F4SG Grant</title>
      <link>/services/grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/grant/</guid>
      <description>A research grant to work on forecasting for social good research
Forecasting for Social Good Research Grant The Forecasting for Social Good (FSG) research grant aims to draw together researchers and practitioners, from developing and developed countries, to advance forecasting knowledge and its link to decision making, influence forecasting for social good practices and drive developments.
This research grant is being organized and sponsored by Dr. Bahman Rostami-Tabar, Technology Futures, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahmed Aziz Ezzat</title>
      <link>/team/aziz-ezzat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aziz-ezzat/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democratising Forecasting</title>
      <link>/services/democratising-forecasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/democratising-forecasting/</guid>
      <description>This is an ongoing initiative sponsored by the International Institute of Forecasters that provides cutting-edge training on forecasting.
Democratising Forecasting This is an ongoing initiative that provides cutting-edge training in the area of forecasting using R in some of the world’s least developed countries and organisations with social missions. The workshop is free of charge.
The project is initiated and delivered by Dr. Bahman Rostami-Tabar and sponsored by the International Institute of Forecasters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shraddhanand Shukla</title>
      <link>/team/shraddhanand-shukla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/shraddhanand-shukla/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mingzhi shi</title>
      <link>/team/mingzhi-shi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/mingzhi-shi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F4SG Data Repository</title>
      <link>/services/repository/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/repository/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Book Club</title>
      <link>/services/book-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/book-club/</guid>
      <description>We read, debate and discuss forecasting related books, join us.
What is the Forecasting Book club? We would like to create an online learning environment dedicated to sharing knowledge in the area of forecasting to be inclusive to the largest number of learners and contributors. I believe nothing can compare to the knowledge you gain through reading books. Therefore, we created this community to read and discuss forecasting related books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buket Cilali</title>
      <link>/team/buket-cilali/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/buket-cilali/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hussain Syed Kazmi</title>
      <link>/team/hussain-kazmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/hussain-kazmi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please feel free to get in touch for any enquiry and if you would like to support the forecasting for social good initiatives by donation or volunteering your time
   Project Contact     F4SG Workshop Buket Cilali   F4SG Grant Bahman Rostami-Tabar   Democratising Forecasting Ahmed Aziz Ezzat   Book Club Mingzhi shi   Data Repository Hussain Syed Kazmi   F4G Research Network Michael Porter    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About forecasting for social good</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>What is Forecasting for Social Good? What is the point of forecasting? If asked this question, most academics and practitioners would say ‘to inform better decisions’, or words to that effect. This immediately prompts two further questions: i) what do we mean by better? and ii) better for whom? Most of the organisations in which a more professional and analytical approach to forecasting is employed have economic and financial goals, such as minimising costs or maximising profits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
