<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Forecasting for Social Good</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Forecasting for Social Good</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:33:46 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>F4SG annual workshop</title>
      <link>/services/f4sg-workshoop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/f4sg-workshoop/</guid>
      <description>This is an annual workshop sponsored by the International Institute of Forecasters
Forecasting for Social Good Workshop While there is a growing recognition by agencies, organizations, and governments that data-driven decision making tools, like forecasting models, can offer significant improvements to the societies they are working to improve, there is not a cohesive body of research that offers guidance on how to best implement, understand, use, and evaluate forecasting methods for societal impact in practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democratising Forecasting</title>
      <link>/services/democratising-forecasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/democratising-forecasting/</guid>
      <description>This is an ongoing initiative sponsored by the International Institute of Forecasters that provides cutting-edge training on forecasting.
Democratising Forecasting This is an ongoing initiative that provides cutting-edge training in the area of forecasting using R in some of the world’s least developed countries and organisations with social missions. The workshop is free of charge.
The project is initiated and delivered by Dr. Bahman Rostami-Tabar and sponsored by the International Institute of Forecasters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
